Will you catch it?   Hey, do
n't say too much, okay.  It's my swing, I wo
n't let you swing.  I have a rope.  I have a
flat surface.  It's my tree, I won't let you swing on it.
What will you do?
Well, it's your pata.  It was stuck but I could
not insert it for long.  If I put it in, I am getting a lot of bids.   You
swung as much as you could from the branch.
You have swung so much.  Ok.   One should
not show so much arrogance about other's things.
Ok.
Ok.  I see it's none of your business.   Will
not come.  Go.
Go run away from here.   Come on
son.
What did you put?  She has come to fight.
[Music] I'm having
trouble with Poonam.
No, no, I will not cut it from here.  I
will cut it from the top and leave it a little so that when you
guys start swinging, you fall.
[Music]
This swing went swinging.   Are you
enjoying it?
Yes.
Enjoyed very much.   The
breeze feels so nice, doesn't it?  From today onwards, it's all
fun, fun,
fun, I am I am
Mummy,
Mummy, I am I am
how did you bring the rope, Sarla, now sister, you had
brought a strong rope, I don't know how it broke, I
think someone cut it, it is not broken, oh
they fell down.  [laughter]
Well, well, well, well.
Wait, I will pick it up.
Not going anywhere.  Yes.  Our children were
not allowed to swing.  Yes.  I had
worked so hard to get it swung.  Even if it falls, even if it falls.
[laughter] The
rope was strong.  Couldn't break.  You are the one who
cut it, right?
You saw it.
[Laughter]